## TEMI BABALOLA

Toronto, Ontario/+1 437-223-4327 babalolaife@yahoo.com

October 12, 2022

The Hiring Manager,

Dear Sir/Madam,

This letter is to express my interest in the job posted on your website for a web developer intern. I am currently taking a graduate certificate course in Web development at Humber College. I have good understanding of some programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Json and ASP.net; combined with my communication and problem-solving skills. Building state-of-the-art, easy, friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine and I confident that I would be an excellent candidate for the Software Developer Intern role at your organization.

I have great interpersonal skills and enjoy working in teams as this helps to collaborate and learn from others. I have a proactive personality, and a desire to deliver my best work at every point in time. I have a love for improving software development workflows/process. I am curious and I enjoy work that challenges me to learn something new and stretch in a different direction.

While I worked as a HR professional, I noticed that most of our tasks were being automated and this led me to develop an interest in computer programming. I do my best to stay on top of changes, as the world keeps evolving everyday so I can meet challenges with tools well suited to the job at hand. I am a great communicator and hardworking.

I have attached a copy of my resume detailing my education and experience. I look forward to sharing more about my skills and experiences. I can be reached anytime by phone at 437-223-4327 or email at babalolaife@yahoo.com.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to speaking with you soon.

Yours sincerely,

Temi Babalola

# TEMI BABALOLA

Toronto, Ontario/+1 437-223-4327

babalolaife@yahoo.com

## PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

Web developer intern with experience in Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node JS, React. Passionate about web development and excited to learn more. Skilled in problem solving and working independently as well as in a team.

## **SKILLS SET:**

- Good understanding of JavaScript (Vue, Nuxt, Angula)
- ➤ Experience with the use of HTML, CSS, SQL, Json and ASP.net
- > Focus on details and quality at both the code level and the overall application design
- > Highly initiative and exhibit creative thinking
- > Effective interpersonal and communication skills
- ➤ Knowledge of different solution development methodologies (Waterfall, Agile)
- > Strong analytical skill
- Ability to troubleshoot problems and recommend solutions
- ➤ Ability to work independently with minimal supervision and as part of a team
- > Proficient with use of MS Office tools

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

ISMILE TECHNOLOGIES, ILLINOIS, CHICAGO Human Resource Analyst	Jun 2020 – Jan 2022
SMARTWATT TECHNOLOGIES, LAGOS Human Resource Coordinator	Jul 2015 – Sep 2018
GUARANTY TRUST BANK PLC, LAGOS Customer Service Assistant Manager	Nov 2013 – Feb 2015
GUARANTY TRUST BANK PLC, LAGOS Customer Service Officer	May 2011 – Oct 2013
EDUCATION:	
Graduate Certificate Program (Web Development) Humber College	Ongoing
Graduate Certificate Program (Human Resources Management) Seneca College	2019
Bachelor of Science Degree (Accounting) Covenant University	2009